blinkbits.com 2005-12-28

# Company Bits Company Bits - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy 

Blink Bits is committed to taking the appropriate measures and precautions to safeguard the privacy of Blink Bits members. Our Online Privacy Policy continues our commitment to serve you and to protect your privacy online. 

Our privacy pledge to you: We will not collect any personal information from you that you do not volunteer, and Blink Bits are the sole owners of all information collected on this site. We do not sell, share, or rent this information to others in any way that we have not mentioned in this statement. 

When you sign up to become a member on Blink Bits, we collect personal information about you such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card information, user name and password. When personal information is being collected, you will know because you will have to fill out a form and submit. 

If you are a Blink Bits member, we will not sell, rent, swap, or authorize any third party to use any information that specifically identifies you. 

Email Policy: Account-Related Email: We will send you e-mails relating to your account. These include order watch list emails, notifications of private messages, notifications of group messages, confirmations, renewal/expiration notices, and credit card problem notifications. 

Email Newsletters: We may offer email newsletters which will inform you of special Blink Bits promotions and announcements. If you no longer wish to receive a specific newsletter you can simply follow the 'unsubscribe' instructions located near the bottom of each newsletter. 

Except by way of acquisition, asset purchase agreement, merger or operating agreement, we will not we will not sell, rent, swap, or authorize any third party to use an email address of a Blink Bits member 

Security and Passwords: We maintain a secure process to collect, transmit and store your personal information. We urge you to keep your password in a safe place and not to divulge it to anyone. Also, please remember to sign off your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit to Blink Bits. This ensures that others cannot access your account, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place such as a library or Internet cafe. 

Contact Us: If you have any questions or concerns about the Blink Bits Privacy Policy or its implementation, please feel free to contact us at Blink Bits, Privacy Policy, Ponte Vedra, FL 32082 or email us at privacy@Blink Bits.com. 

This policy was last revised March 2005.
